Guide to the Agenda Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- November 2001 Acquisition, 1972-2000; 6; 17.21; (18 boxes)
  - David Messmer's File
    - "Miscellaneous Considerations," writings, 1994; 2 (Box 81)
    - Cole, Peter. Speech's Hedge: poems and a pamphlet, typescript, 1995 September 18 (Box 81)
    - Bantock, Gavin. SeaManShip: nine configurations, typescript, 1996 October 4 (Box 81)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 81)
    - Cole, Brian. Writing sample, typescript, 1995 July 15 (Box 81)
    - Material taken for issues afer Autumn 1992; after Tom Scott; correspondence; Geoffrey Hill, etc., circa 1992-1993; 2 (Box 81)
  - Restricted Fragile Material
    Box 82 (computer disks): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies are available. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Computer disks (20011107-a.0001 - 20011107-a.0005), undated (Box 82)
- October 2007 Acquisition, 1983-2001; 7; 1; (1 box)
  This portion of the collection contains production material for volume 37, numbers 2-4 (1999-2000), correspondence, and writings.
  Formerly classed as Uncat MSS 983.
  - Dale, Peter. "Sonnets," typescript, undated (Box 83)
  - Dale, Peter. "Too Much Water," typescript, 1983 (Box 83)
  - Milne, W. S. "Geoffrey Hill," first draft, typescript, undated (Box 83)
  - O'Hara, Francis. "Poems," typescript, undated (Box 83)
  - Thomas, R. S. Correspondence, circa 1998 (Box 83)
  - Whitby, Julie. "Poems for Lovers," typescripts, 1999; 2 (Box 83)
  - [Volume 34, Number 2], "Geoffrey Hill Issue, etc.," writings, 1996 (Box 83)
  - [Volume 37, Numbers 3-4], "Thom Gunn Issue," author's proofs, 1999 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence, 1996-1999; 3 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence and writings, 2001 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence and writings, undated (Box 83)
  - Westminster School 40th Anniversary Party, correspondence and guest list, 1994 (Box 83)